Lost instructions slow small businesses down. Binders, shared drives, group chats, and "ask someone who knows" all cost time.
TechSavvy SOP Portal gives your team one branded home for the procedures they use every day.
Staff can search by keyword, role, department, section, or daily workflow, then open the exact approved SOP they need.
Every SOP can include a QR code, so employees can scan, open, and follow the right procedure on a phone or tablet, right where the work happens.
Instead of hunting through documents, staff see the purpose, steps, attachments, validation notes, roles, and review status together on one clean screen.
Managers can build the process library faster with AI-assisted SOP generation, then import existing procedure documents when you already have content to reuse.
The editor keeps process details organized: owners, sections, roles, review dates, steps, validation, attachments, and approval workflow all stay in one place.
When procedures change, version history and approvals help protect the current process, so staff are not relying on outdated instructions.
Training tools turn written procedures into accountability. Add quiz questions, track training runs, and confirm that staff understand the work.
Checklists turn repeatable work into daily action. Employees can complete task runs, add notes, and leave a clear record of what was done.
When something is missing, outdated, or unclear, staff can suggest a change. Managers review, approve, and keep everyone using the current version.
The manager dashboard gives leaders a quick view of SOP health, drafts, requests, user access, and the work that needs attention.
Role-based access helps each person see what matters to their job, while managers keep control over users, logins, assignments, and permissions.
Brand settings let every customer portal feel like their own, with company name, portal name, colors, logo, staff rules, mobile links, and QR settings.
Built-in support requests give staff and managers a simple way to ask for help without losing the context of the portal.
Backup, restore, export, and retention tools make the portal practical to support after launch, not just easy to demonstrate.
The result is less repeated training, fewer wrong steps, faster onboarding, and better protection for the knowledge that keeps your business running.
TechSavvy SOP Portal is built for growing businesses with 5 to 250 users. Give your team one current answer, wherever the work happens. Book a demo.